smallbusiness.wa.gov.au 2016-06-25

# Legal information

We comply with the [standards of the State Government of Western Australia](http://www.finance.wa.gov.au/cms/content.aspx?id=16137 "Department of finance website opens in a new window") for security, privacy, copyright, links to external websites, how we handle email and use information. Our agency-specific legal information is available below.

  1. [Copyright](http://www.smallbusiness.wa.gov.au/business-in-wa/about-sbdc/legal-information/#copyright "copyright")
  2. [Links to external websites](http://www.smallbusiness.wa.gov.au/business-in-wa/about-sbdc/legal-information/#links "links")
  3. [Privacy](http://www.smallbusiness.wa.gov.au/business-in-wa/about-sbdc/legal-information/#privacy "privacy")
  4. [Security](http://www.smallbusiness.wa.gov.au/business-in-wa/about-sbdc/legal-information/#security "security")

The materials presented on the Small Business Development Corporation (the Corporation) web pages are provided voluntarily as a service to our clients.

The information and advice provided is made available in good faith and is derived from sources believed to be reliable and accurate at the time of release on the internet. However, the information is provided solely on the basis that readers will be responsible for making their own assessment of the matters discussed herein and that they should verify all relevant representations, statements and information.

Neither the Corporation nor its officers take any responsibility for that statement or representation, nor shall the Corporation or any of its officers be liable in respect of any such statement or representation, whether by reason of negligence, lack of care, or for any other reason whatsoever.

Much of the information on this site is a summary only. Visitors should consult the appropriate source material for full information concerning legal rights or responsibilities.

## Copyright

### Small Business Development Corporation

Unless otherwise stated, copyright of all material published within any SBDC website is reserved by the Small Business Development Corporation. All rights are reserved.

Images, text and all other files which comprise any SBDC website are provided for educational and reference purposes only. You may download, display, print and reproduce this material in unaltered form only (retaining this note) for your personal, non-commercial use or use within your organisation.

Apart from any use as permitted under the provisions of the _Copyright Act 1968_ , no part of this website may be reproduced or re-used in any material form or transmitted to any other person for any purposes whatsoever without the prior written permission from the Small Business Development Corporation.

Requests and inquiries concerning reproduction and rights should be addressed to:

## Links to external websites

Material on this website includes hypertext links to external websites not hosted on our domain (http://smallbusiness.wa.gov.au).

Links to external websites are provided, in good faith, as a service only and do not represent endorsement or recommendation of any information, company, product or service. It is the responsibility of the internet user to make his or her own decisions about the accuracy, currency, reliability and correctness of information found on those sites.

## Privacy

Protecting your privacy and your personal information is important to us. While Western Australian Government agencies are not regulated by the _Privacy Act 1988_ , we will respect and protect the privacy of our users and strive to achieve best practice at all times.

The Small Business Development Corporation's (SBDC) websites do not automatically collect information that would identify individual visitors. On the rare occasion that we may  collect personal information this would only be with your consent. You can access any SBDC website without disclosing personal information.

The following information is routinely collected for statistical purposes when you visit one of our websites:

  * server address;
  * top level domain name (for example .com; .gov; .au; .org );
  * date and time of your visit;
  * pages accessed and documents downloaded; and
  * address of previous website visited and the type of browser used.

No attempt is made to identify individual users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider's logs.

### Email management and collection of personal information

We will record your personal information (including email address) if you send us a message, register for a workshop/event, subscribe to our e-newsletter or join a survey/interest group.

The information you provide may be added to our customer relationship management system (CRM) and used for future communications from us. We will also use any additional contact information you provide to assist us in responding to your questions or enquiries, and to confirm your appointments, or workshop and event bookings.

We will not use or disclose your personal information to any third party.

Subscribers to our e-newsletter can unsubscribe at any time.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of information that a website sends to your browser when you access information at that site. Our websites use cookies to track usage patterns and traffic trends, and to improve the user's experience.

## Security

The Small Business Development Corporation uses industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to ensure the highest security for credit card and personal details submitted to the Corporation over the internet. Our security certificate is issued by [GeoTrust](http://www.geotrust.com/au/about/ "GeoTrust opens in a new window") and uses Domain Validated SSL with 2048 Bit encryption. Your personal information will be encrypted by your own computer or device at a bit rate determined by the browser you are using, before it is sent to the Corporation.
